Ruslan Korneev

shaggybackend@gmail.com +381631256805 Belgrade, Serbia

Summary

Python Backend Developer with about 4 years experience. Based in Belgrade, Serbia. Looking for new opportunities in Belgrade or United States(ready to relocate). Open to remote work as well, full-time or part-time.

I'd love to join great friendly company, where I can feel family atmosphere, where we would share to each other something interesting and new from IT-world

Contacts

- Telegram
- Linked In
- Github

Experience

Python Backend Developer

Vision Systems • Belgrade 05/2023

· Building a backend using Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, Postgres

Python Backend Developer

Kortechs • Belgrade, Serbia 04/2022 - 04/2023

- Built a SlackBot to control a GitLab's projects/repositories, monitoring ci/cd pipelines via slack, notifications, e.t.c.
- Was building an <u>Altaport</u> project from scratch. This is web-application, Reservation system for pilots operators and heliport/airport managers. Stack: Django REST, Postgres, Redis, Celery, React-Typescript. Made an integrations with TimeKit, SendGrid(Twillio), Stripe and other systems.

Python Backend Developer

Corpberry • Rostov-on-Don, Russia 09/2021 - 04/2022

- Scraping and Parsing using Python(requests, beautifulsoup4, pandas, boto3), AWS-S3, Google Sheets
- Scripts to parse a large sources using a regex and python, save to db and output using Django Templates.
- Fixing a bugs in some legacy projects written on Diango REST and writing tests using pytest, pytest-diango.
- Setting up Grafana-Prometheus for Django-Postgres project for monitoring and statistics.

Python Backend Developer

NiceCode • Rostov-on-Don, Russia 01/2021 - 09/2021

- Was maintaining an existing project <u>reLife</u>. On backend side we were using python, django rest, postgres, daphne, redis, celery, payment system leopay, aws s3. On frontend side react, js.
- Built a Telegram Bot which monitoring the added servers, sending notifications if something is broken, or the memory is close to die. Stack: python, aiogram, django-admin.

Python Backend Developer

Supplar • Rostov-on-Don, Russia 05/2020 - 01/2021

Built an Application Server from scratch using Python, Django REST Framework, Postgres for Mobile application written

in a Dart, Flutter.

Supplar App is generator of daily recipes for everybody, depends on your preferences, such as height, weight, allergies, calories, proteins, fats, carbohydrates and e.t.c

Python Backend - Freelance

Self-employed • Part Time 06/2019 - 05/2020

- Python Backend Development: Django REST, Postgres, Celery, Redis
- Web-Scraping: python, requests, beautifulsoup4, selenium
- Telegram/Slack bots: python, aiogram, asyncio, aiohttp
- · Mentoring for beginners in python development

Skills

Python, Django, Postgres, Redis, Celery, RESTful API, Linux, Git, Github Actions, Gitlab CI, Docker, Kubernetes

Education

Python Backend Development

GeekBrains • Moscow, Russia 09/2022

Faculty of Nuclear Sciences and Physical Engineering

Czech Technical University of Prague • Prague, Czech 09/2021

Czech Language

GoStudy • Prague, Czech 09/2020

Languages

English, Russian, Czech